[{"answer": "Well, if in fact he had anything to do with the bombing of 103, that is either by way of transmitting the order or giving the orders, then he could be tried by a Scottish court.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "Judge Mukasey, what is the legal position with this man as we stand today?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "I think they'll be given the chance to talk to him.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Will they be given that chance, do you think?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "As an American, obviously to the extent that somebody has it in mind to get rid of Gadhafi, that's all to the good.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "What do you make of what is happening in Libya right now just -- as an American and as a judge?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Well, Moussa Koussa should be given a really cushy cell somewhere, and I understand that he needs medical treatment, and that would be great, as well.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "Would you ever see a position where you would trade immunity for people like Moussa Koussa in return for the capture of Gadhafi himself?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "What you had in Kuwait was the resignation of the government.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 121, "question": "What was that?", "qSentId": 120}, {"answer": "I predict uncertainty for quite a bit of time.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "Do you predict economic turmoil for quite -- some considerable time?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "So I went there just to thank our colleagues who have been doing an amazing job in our Tokyo office, and nothing, Piers, prepared me.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "And what did you find?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "So in the short term, this is a headwind for everybody, because it disrupts demand, it disrupts supply chains.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Or in terms of economy, are they able to withstand it on their own?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "Is your general advice to the American consumer tighten the belt a bit?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "It's going to be a bumpy ride.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "Going to be a bumpy ride?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "A star everything, yes.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "If there's one thing you need to know about my next guest is don't bet against Dwayne Johnson, the man you may known as \"The Rock,\" is a star in the ring, a star in Hollywood, a star -- just about a star everything, aren't you?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "I would have to say -- I would have to say growing up and the examples that were set for me from my parents.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "What do you think that has come from?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "No, I didn't.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "Did you ever imagine you'd reach the stage where you're a $10 million-a-movie star?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "OHNSON: Well, I think a good portion it is, sure.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "And you say that's mainly from your parents, you think?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "Oh, my god.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "Mr. President, are you OK?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "Well, the -- certainly the ones that you just mentioned, sure, and plus I think, you know, growing up in Hawaii -- Hawaii's a very warm and proud place to grow up.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "When you look at what's happened with Barack Obama, do you see parallels with your life?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "I've talked to the phone with him.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Have you met him?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "Oh, many private things, Piers.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "What was that about?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Sure -- you know, I thought about it.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "You ever think maybe I'll have a go?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "Ultimate power, you're the president of the United States of America.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Well, in what way?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "I would be passionate about taking care of our troops and protecting our troops.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "What are the things that would really be passionate to you?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "They have.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "Has anyone said that before?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "I think he's doing a great job, and I'm very, very proud of him.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "How do you think -- how do you think he's doing?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "I'm open to it.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "But everyone is asking one question, are you ever going to get back and start wrestling again?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Very open to it.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 362, "question": "You are?", "qSentId": 361}, {"answer": "We do.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "You still work together, right?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "My expectation -- my expectation of marriage, you know, I don't quite know what my expectation of marriage was back then.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "What was your expectation of marriage?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "I can't tell you that.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Who's the lucky girl in your life now then?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "Well, privacy's important to me and it's important -- you know, my relationships -- the relationships I have, whether it -- regardless of who it is, whether it's my girlfriend, ex-wife's little girl friends, whatever it is, it -- it's always been important to me to be private and live privately.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "How have you managed to achieve that?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Or has it put you off for life going through a bad divorce?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "You know that, you know?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "Well, to say -- it was genius.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "-- was genius, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "One's a former federal officer, spent five years in deep cover.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Is all this really necessary to apprehend two men?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Can you remember them?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "What were they?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "He has, yes.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "Has he told you that he loves you now?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "Being a good dad is one.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "What else would you put in there?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "I would love to, sure.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "Like to win an Oscar?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "Sure, I would love to.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Practiced your speech?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "My mom.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Who's the one person you believe -- if you had to choose one -- you owe most to?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "I'm on Piers Morgan today.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 630, "question": "If I was to ask you, Jerry Weintraub is -- what would you say?", "qSentId": 629}, {"answer": "You know, it's hard for me to describe myself.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "But how would you describe yourself?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "He was a great guy.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "What was he like -- Sinatra?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "I think they're -- well, Sinatra knew how to tell a story in song.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "What do you think separates the good from the great when it comes to stars?", "qSentId": 683}, {"answer": "Sure, it is.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 689, "question": "Is it the same thing?", "qSentId": 688}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "You sad to see her go?", "qSentId": 698}, {"answer": "The women love him.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 717, "question": "And who's the woman?", "qSentId": 716}, {"answer": "I think right now of all the ladies, depending on the kind of role it is, Angie -- Angelina Jolie is brilliant.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "Who's the woman?", "qSentId": 718}, {"answer": "Will Smith.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 735, "question": "And who would you pick to play you in a movie?", "qSentId": 734}, {"answer": "Well, I haven't pulled it off.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 745, "question": "How have you pulled this off, Jerry?", "qSentId": 744}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 791, "question": "Well, you picked very good women, haven't you?", "qSentId": 790}, {"answer": "I've been lucky twice.", "docId": "110331pmt", "aSentId": 793, "question": "That's the trick, isn't it?", "qSentId": 792}]